

polina.v.peneva@gmail.com 0876 808 886

polinapeneva.com 🥽

Hello, my name is Polina and I am web and graphic designer and artist who is about to graduate this year with a B.A. degree in Fine Arts. With this backround I get unique design aesthetic. When I started learning in SoftUni Creative in 2019 I transitioned to design. I'm currently 26 years old and located in Sofia, Bulgaria. I am striving to secure a design position to use my creative skills and knowledge I am passionate about expressing ideas in creative ways.

## **SKILLS**

Adobe Illustato	Adobe Phot	oshop Adobe 2	e XD Adobe InDesign		Adobe Premier Pro		Adobe After Effects	Figma
Prototyping	User research	Storyboarding Pa		ainting and Drawing	Illustrating			

### **EDUCATION**

## Academy SoftUni Creative

10/2019 - Present

- UX Design Advanced
- Logo Design with Illustrator
- Illustrator Advanced
- UI Design
- Graphic Design with InDesign

- Figma
- Game Modelling with Maya
- Video Processing with Premiere Pro
- UX Web Design
- Graphic Design with Photoshop

# Bachelor's degree

New Bulgarian Univesity

09/2014 - Present

- Plastic Arts
- Specialty: Contemporary painting and murals

## **High School**

National High School of Applied Arts "St. Luka"

09/2009 - 05/2014

- Applied arts

Specialty: Textile Design

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Ataro Clima Ltd

Technical assistant

11/2019 - Present Leader in building installations business Sofia, Bulgaria

- Achievements/Tasks
- Responsible for supporting business operations by doing administrative and technical tasks under a direct supervisor
- Acquired strong time management and multitasking skills to perform tasks in a fast-paced environment and high-level operations
- Preparation of reports, presentations and others
- Communication with clients

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Work and Travel USA

Fresh Nantucket; Stop and Shop; The Juice Bar

06/2019 - 09/2019

A work and travel program - student brigade in the United States

- Achievements/Tasks
- Improved English level
- Work in an international environment
- Observing different models and strategies for successful business
- Successfully adapted to new surroundings and becoming absolutely independent

# Studio Moderna Bulgaria

Agent Telemarketing

04/2014 - 08/2014

- Acquired qualities
- Sales and communication technique
- Learned to be more resilient, to handle rejection and not to give up
- Communicating with people of all types
- Emotional quotient how to communicate using empathy at all times to your advantage

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication Skills Adaptability Teamwork Attention to detail Creativity Design aptitude Problem Solving

Negotiation Collaboration Organization Responsibility Fast learning Curiosity Color Aptitude

## **PROJECTS**

https://mnky.bg/

Website for irrigation systems made on WordPress

Polly Peneva Art

Personal brand

Behance.net/polipeneva

## **INTERESTS**

Drawing

Reading books

Traveling

Photography

Nantucket, USA

Sofia, Bulgaria